Hina was anxious with a lot on her mind.
Why not fried chicken and rolled omelette?
What do you think of that?
And what about sweet and salty kinkura?
No! Nothing brown!
It has to be a cute luncheon!
Brown is not cute!
Maybe you can't understand.
It has to be like...
Ta-da!
Then he'll be a...
Wow, how cute!
But he's a middle school boy, isn't he?
Don't you think he might be more interested in...
Something that's delicious looking rather than cute?
What do you think, Ray?
How'd you peel so many?
You did that really fast!
Oh, yeah.
Tomorrow is Sunday.
You're so precise.
You're really good with your hands.
I'm glad you came over.
I have over eight pounds of these.
The baseball team from Hina's middle school will be having a game.
You know, I've never tried eating chestnuts before.
They look kind of interesting.
I wonder if there's something I'd like.
Definitely.
It's the perfect winter snack.
And if you boil it down to a pulp, it lasts a long time.
Hina has a crush on one of the players.
She's going to his game tomorrow to cheer him on.
Takahashi's the son of a milkman.
He's pretty tall for a boy his age.
He must have grown up drinking lots of milk as a boy.
It's funny.
He used to be shorter than Hina back in grade school.
But now, he's an ace baseball player and very popular at Hina's school.
Hina's been putting a lot of effort into making Takahashi a perfect homemade lunch.
It's a big event, and everything has to be just right.
Guess you've got more competition now.
You've liked Takahashi since elementary school, but I guess you're not the only one.
I don't like him!
It's not like that!
Why do you always have to try and make it all romantic?
Stop being stupid!
Sorry, didn't mean to upset you.
It's the night before the big day that she's been waiting for.
And I'm here to witness it.
All while peeling the chestnuts that are ready to be boiled.
What do you think about this stuff?
Think about what?
Let me see.
You want to make pumpkin croquettes shaped like apples in a flower bed made of rice balls?
Boil and mash the pumpkin, cover it with flour, then cut with egg yolk and breadcrumbs.
Let's see.
The game starts at 10, right?
If you leave the house at 9.30, that's cutting it pretty close for the first time making all of this.
You may need more time, and that'll make you nervous.
And the more you rush around in the kitchen, the more likely you'll make mistakes.
Well, what exactly do you think I should do?
Keep it simple.
Fried chicken and rolled omelet.
You could add some color with a cherry tomato.
But is there anything I can eat now?
I don't want to make any of that!
It's like old lady food!
Just forget it!
God!
Oh, lady!
Never mind!
I'll figure it out myself!
Fine then!
Just go ahead and do what you want!
I'm done giving you advice!
It's not like you're listening anyway!
Don't, don't!
No way!
It's already 9!
I think the supermarket's open till 10!
I have no more money!
So, um, hey sis, I want to buy all these ingredients, but I don't have enough money for it, so, um...
Let's take a look.
Winter squash, ground beef, breadcrumbs, onions, eggs, black pepper, radishes, olives, avocado, asparagus, baby corn, balsamic vinegar, lemons, red and yellow...
Make some more!
Why did you stop?
How much are you planning on making?
And how much were you gonna spend?
This isn't cost effective!
This will cost over 3,000 yen!
We don't have that kind of money!
We can't spend 3,000 yen of our own budget just to buy some other kid's lunch!
The only time we splurge on milk for ourselves is when it's on sale for 158 yen!
No!
Excuse me?
Some other kid?
But what about the cats and Ray?
Aren't they the same?
Huh!
What the heck?
Why didn't you get to use our money on people outside the family?
You're not part of my family?
How come you're not Momo's big brother?
Uh, well, I...
I'm sorry.
Help!
This is awkward.
Um, so...
I'm sorry.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
I offered to pay for my share of food before.
It's just that Akari would never accept my money.
Maybe after what happened tonight, she'll change her mind and let me pay.
Then I guess I wouldn't feel so guilty whenever I come over.
Ah!
Akari has a soft spot for all kinds of strays.
Dogs and cats.
Anything really.
When she sees scrawny strays, she feels bad.
She takes care of them, till they're soft and fluffy again.
But I was surprised when I found out she actually brought a person home one day.
Who, me?
But I don't mind, really.
She'll make you soft and fluffy, too.
She just needs a little more time.
Yeah, you think so?
Hmm.
I see.
Yep.
You'll see.
So on Sunday morning...
I spent so much time making these!
I gotta start all over!
Something's burning!
Apple saute!
It's a fire!
Sloppy, sloppy!
What time is it?
Ain't already you know!
But I woke up at six o'clock!
Who could be calling at this hour?
I'm busy!
Where's Yoko?
I'm running a little late.
Just leave without me.
There.
What should I wear?
I was so focused on lunch that I didn't even think about what I should wear!
Maybe this is too flashy.
Does this make me look desperate for his attention?
How'd it get so late so fast?
Curtains are more expensive than I thought.
But now I'll finally be able to sleep in later.
I don't have any matches coming up for a while.
So this is a good opportunity to get everything that I need for the apartment.
I still need a chair, a desk, a bookshelf.
Huh?
Oh, they're having a game at Hina's middle school.
Oh, it's the famous Takahashi.
He's huge!
I can't believe he's only in middle school.
He seems like a pretty cool guy, though.
There's Hina.
She looks excited.
I wonder if she made his luncheon time.
Let's go!
Huh?
Whoa!
It's a slowback!
Takahashi!
A home run?
You're welcome!
You're welcome, Takahashi!
Yay!
He did it all right!
That was so cool.
He knocked it out of the park.
He totally looks like the main character from some boy's manga.
I've never seen Hina act like this before.
She is clearly smitten with this guy.
This is real for her.
I think she could be falling in love.
Love.
Thank you.
After getting dressed, we're heading to Matsuda.
Ah, Matsuda?
For Monja?
Sounds great!
Is Takahashi around?
Coming, Takahashi?
To Matsuda?
Ah, thanks.
Takahashi?
Are you all right?
Sounds great!
Can we go too?
All right!
Moja it is!
So what should I get?
Come on, Takahashi!
Let's go!
Don't do it.
But what will Akari say about this?
She's gonna ask me why I didn't give it to him.
She'll say after all that trouble, why didn't you?
What?
She'll never understand what it was like for me today.
Why is she crying?
I mean, she's naturally beautiful.
And she's always been a good cook.
So anyone, I'd be happy to have lunch made by her.
She looked so happy last night, and even earlier today.
But now...
All right now, let's go home.
We'll eat it there.
I guess...
I just don't understand girls.
Welcome home!
I see.
You weren't able to give it to him.
Well, that's too bad.
Well, you certainly did your best.
Oh, there, there.
It'll be all right.
I know how you feel.
The exact same thing happened to me before.
I understand.
You weren't able to give someone you liked the lunch you made?
I was just like you.
I didn't have the courage to do it.
I wanted to make the perfect cute lunch so badly.
I think my nerves got to me, and then I failed.
That's why I couldn't help saying what I did.
But later, I remembered something.
You know what I said to you yesterday evening?
It's the same thing that mom had told me when I was your age.
I guess you could say, like mother, like daughter.
Isn't that funny?
Mom said that to you?
So, let's see how it turned out.
Yeah.
What? You want some?
Well, just this once.
Really? I get to have some?
Okay, the tea's finally ready.
Let's eat.
What happened to the kitties?
Looks to me like they ate themselves into a food coma.
So, how is it?
Hina, did you taste this while making it?
It had a bitter taste to it, while also being sweet and sour.
All the flavors you're left with at the end of a first love.
Next time, let me help you in the kitchen.
I'll give it my best shot!
Maybe it's a good thing she wasn't able to give him her first homemade lunch.
At least, that's what Rei and I thought.
She still has a long way to go.
I can see it!
What?
Uh, you know I'm the one who won, right?
Hmm?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
But it was just an anomaly.
Mmm, it's not an anomaly if it happens all the time.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you say so, you won, okay?
Jeez, whatever makes you feel better about it.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are you trying to pull here?
Being all, fine, if you say so, doesn't change anything.
Okay, one more game and I'll go first.
I'll start off with the static rook and you do the bishop exchange once more.
Huh? What the heck?
It's like you're using me as a practice board.
That's it!
You're being petty!
This requires expediency.
We can't allow the bishop exchange to rule the board.
We have to find something that can stop it.
Huh?
If you want to win, you should use the ranging rook.
But I like using the static rook!
You won't even let me practice the move I'm still not good at.
Eh, whatever.
How many times do I have to tell you that I would prefer to study by myself?
We raise each other up, you and I.
You'd be losing out on a very important part of your shogi life without our rivalry!
You understand that, don't you?
Kiriyama!
Time is of the essence and the two of us need to find it!
We can't waste a single moment!
In fact, you have to be the one that discovers it!
The bishop exchange crusher silver bullet.
Yes!
It's the Nikaido vaccine!
Huh?
If I discover it, it'll be the Kiriyama vaccine!
But it's what I've been dreaming of!
The Nikaido vaccine!
Or the Nikaido system!
I want to leave behind a technique with my name on it!
Don't you understand?
I understand it?
That doesn't mean I agree with it!
Good morning!
You suddenly showed up at 9 in the morning saying something about developing a silver bullet technique.
And besides, I'm an all-rounder, so I'm not interested in that kind of...
Hey, is this getting through to you?
Okay, let's get some lunch.
Where to?
Let's get some fast food.
Oh yeah, how about Mech Burger?
Have you tried the Giga Mech?
You'd probably like it.
The Giga Mech?
We'll pass.
So what do you usually wind up getting for lunch?
Oh, me?
Well, when I'm alone, I guess I usually get a burger or a beef bowl.
It just kind of depends on how I feel.
But lately, I've been having dinner at my friend's house whenever I can.
Is that you, Momo?
What's wrong?
Where are your sisters?
Bado!
Huh?
Kiriyama, do you know this little girl?
Uh, well, yeah.
If I'm not mistaken, it sounded like she yelled Botoro right before she jumped on me.
You know who Botoro is, don't you?
It's an anime masterpiece loved by children, adults, and yours truly.
It's a story about a big, intelligent creature that lives in a beautiful, magical forest.
Bado!
Awesome!
I admit, I do feel a deep connection to Botoro since we're both so bright.
All right, little girl.
Who are you?
What's your name?
Momo!
All right then, Momo.
Let's all walk together.
The traffic is dangerous here, so we should hold hands.
Momo looks much happier with him than she does with me.
I'll see to it personally that we get you safely home.
Oh, there she is!
Momo!
Hey, it looks like she found Rei!
Hi, thanks for taking care of Momo!
Hi, Rei.
So, um, who was your friend?
Oh, no way!
Not you too, Akari.
Her face is all flushed.
Don't tell me she has a weakness for him too!
That guy?
Um, well, you see, he's from Shogi.
I mean, my club!
Nice to meet you.
My name is Harunobu Nikaido.
I'm Rei's best friend and rival.
Have you two eaten yet?
You're both welcome to join us for dinner if you'd like.
Another outsider?
Well, how very kind of you.
Yes, it would be my pleasure.
Come on, Boudou!
Let's vote some more!
This house is old.
It looks like a vintage movie set.
I'm really sorry about my sister.
It's okay.
You don't have anything to apologize for.
Chico, Chico!
Chubby!
Chubby, Chubby!
How do I explain it?
Your friend is just like a strong and vibrant ball!
Wait, like a ball?
I don't think I've ever heard anyone describe a friend like that.
I'm sorry, but Akari's pretty fond of soft and fluffy things.
She can't help herself.
Which would you prefer to have?
We went grocery shopping today so I can make pretty much anything you'd like.
Some fried chicken or maybe a steak?
Fried chick?
I'd rather have something that's bland and light on protein.
I mean, that's okay.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Anything's fine.
You can choose.
Oh, if you insist.
That's unusual.
I guess you have a pretty mature palate.
That's odd.
How can he maintain such a plump physique if that's all he eats?
Maybe he's on a diet!
Oh no!
Then he'll lose that round and shapely form!
I understand.
It probably bothers him to be so big at his age.
A slow metabolism.
What if the situation's even more serious?
No.
No matter how wonderfully soft he is, it doesn't mean a thing unless he's healthy.
It's okay.
Leave your health to me.
It's so delicious.
Sorry for troubling you, Ikari.
I promised you wouldn't say that, remember?
Life's too hard, Ikari.
I can't have any melanin or bamboo shoes.
I just don't know what I can eat anymore.
I can't even enjoy booze like before.
Doc says I can only have a little.
Poor Mr. Yamamoto.
That's awful.
I'll see if I can find some mild...
I didn't take care of my granny or listen to my customers complain about their dietary restrictions for nothing!
There you are.
Season it however you like to suit your taste, Saranobu.
Delicious!
Even though it's kind of bland.
I'm so glad you like it.
Chew well and eat slowly, okay?
Right.
My butler always tells me I should slow down and chew each bite at least 30 times.
Except I find I'm always too impatient.
Well, I guess you're lucky he cares that much.
Huh?
Who could be visiting us at this hour of the night?
Terribly sorry to disturb you this evening.
It looks like the young master has been enjoying your hospitality.
Hey, Hanaoka!
Did you come here to pick me up?
So you're Harunobu's butler.
I'm surprised you were able to find us.
It wasn't hard.
I just used a GPS.
Oh, excuse me.
I may have a touch of bronchitis.
Nevertheless, I just happened to be passing by.
He always manages to pick me up no matter where I am and never fails to find me.
Guess it's always been like that.
Just like magic.
Magic?
Wait a second, Nikaido.
Don't you know you're under total surveillance?
He just said GPS.
I know that's what he just said.
So if you'd like, please enjoy these treats, everyone.
They're from a local confectionery shop you may have already heard about.
They're my personal favorite.
Please enjoy some.
How nice.
Thanks so much.
Oh my.
What a coincidence.
These are my favorite cakes as well.
How lovely.
Please come in and join us if you'd like.
I'll put on some tea, alright?
Oh, don't mind if I do.
Thank you.
I'm so glad you can join us.
Hina, would you boil some water?
Okay.
He was a close friend of my dad's.
Even though he was an adult, he always treated me with respect.
Tell me, Ray, do you want to play more Shogi?
What's wrong?
Watch the next episode of March Comes In Like A Lion!
I swear, I won't mess up the next lunch I make!
Book 3
I can't eat that섯, but he asked me her to do.
Wow!
She was in love, thank you and God.
Xi, Hallelujah!
Look, you've moved her!